So you're vibe coding or maybe you're
所以你正在进行基于氛围的编程，或者
doing some AI assisted development and
进行一些人工智能辅助开发，
you want to figure out which is the best
你想找出哪个
tool to use. So I usually build out apps
工具最好用。 所以我通常
and prototypes using cursor on this
在这个频道上使用 Cursor 来构建应用程序和原型
channel. But Claude Code has piqued my
。 但最近几个月，Claude Code 引起了我的
interest over the last couple of months
兴趣，
because it's gaining a lot more traction
因为它获得了越来越多的关注，
and it's becoming more and more mature
并且
as a development tool. So, in this
作为一款开发工具也变得越来越成熟。 所以，在这段
video, I'm going to give you a
视频中，我将为大家带来
beginner's introduction to Claw Code,
Claw Code 的入门介绍，讲解
how I use it alongside Cursor, what are
我如何将它与 Cursor 一起使用，
its strengths and weaknesses, when I
它的优点和缺点是什么，什么时候我
would use cursor over Claude and vice
会用 Cursor 代替 Claude，反之亦然
versa, and I'm going to share my
，我还会分享我
opinionated favorite without sitting on
个人最喜欢的，不会
the fence. Not only am I going to show
模棱两可。 我不仅要向
you how to use Claude code, we're
你展示如何使用 Claude 代码，我们还要
actually going to build a functioning
实际构建一个功能齐全的
micro SAS that you could actually use in
微型 SAS，你可以在
your own business or sell on to somebody
自己的企业中使用，也可以卖给其他人
else. So, with the app that we're going
。 所以，通过我们即将
to create, I'm going to be able to drop
开发的这款应用，我就可以把
in an invoice. It's going to be uploaded
发票放进去。 它将被上传
to OpenAI to be processed. OpenAI is
到 OpenAI 进行处理。  OpenAI
going to parse the image and extract all
将解析图像，并将所有
the relevant information into a format
相关信息提取成
that's usable that I can then connect
可用的格式，然后我可以将其连接
into QuickBooks or Zero to reconcile my
到 QuickBooks 或 Zero 来核对我的
invoices. Sell this as a microsass and
发票。 把它作为微型软件出售，就能给
stream for yourself. So, hopefully you
自己带来一笔不错的持续收入。 希望
find my lessons useful. If you want to
我的课程对你有所帮助。 如果你想
go deeper on this topic, there's a huge
深入了解这个主题，这里有一个内容丰富的
course in there which takes you all the
课程，它会带你
way from beginner to advanced in terms
从入门到精通，教你如何运用我
about in my videos. So, in order to get
在视频中提到的所有原则来启动你自己的 AI 应用程序。 所以，为了进行
set up, we just go to Antropic Clawude
设置，我们只需访问 Antropic Clawude
Code and you're going to need to have
Code，并且您需要
NodeJS installed version 18 or up. So,
安装 NodeJS 版本 18 或更高版本。 所以，
just type in Node-V and you'll get your
只需输入 Node-V，即可获得
version number. And I'm on version 22,
版本号。 我用的是 22 版本，
so I'm good. Then you want to copy this
所以没问题。 然后你需要复制这条
little command here, mpm install general
小命令：mpm install general
anthropics. And we can just paste that
anthropics。 我们可以直接粘贴这条
command in. I'm just going to hit
命令。我只需按
return. Now we can just type in claude
回车键即可。 现在我们只需输入 claude
and hit return. And it should give you
然后按回车键即可。 它应该会显示
this welcome screen. You can just pick
这个欢迎界面。 你可以直接选择
dark mode. So you have two different
深色模式。 所以你现在有两种不同的
options here. You can go with the uh
选择。 你可以选择使用
anthropic console using API usage
API 使用
billing or you can go with a
量计费的 uh anthropic 控制台，也可以选择
subscription account. So, if you're
订阅帐户。 所以，如果你
using the console, it's build per
使用控制台，它是按需构建的
request, and it gets pretty expensive uh
，很快就会变得非常昂贵
quickly. So, I generally don't recommend
。 所以，我一般不建议
that. You can rack up a lot of costs
这样做。 很快就会累积很多费用
pretty quick. At minimum, go for the $20
。 至少要选择 20 美元的
pro tier, which gives you access to uh
专业版，这样你就可以访问
Sonnet 4, Claude Sonnet 4, which is
Sonnet 4、Claude Sonnet 4，这
basically your workhorse model, the one
基本上是你的主力模型，
that you're going to use for the
你将在
majority of implementation. Now, you
大部分实施过程中使用它。 现在，您
don't get access to Opus, which is a
无法使用 Opus，而 Opus
Sonnet on the Pro tier. You only get
在 Pro 级别中比 Claude Sonnet 的评级略高一些。 只有付费
that access at the $100 tier. And with
100美元的套餐才能获得该权限。 这样一来
that, you get access to Opus up to a
，你就可以在
certain point before you get rate
一定范围内访问 Opus，之后就会受到速率
limited and it switches down to Claude
限制，并切换到 Claude
Sonnet. Personally,
Sonnet。 就我个人而言，
everybody talks a lot about Opus being,
大家都在谈论 Opus，
you know, a gamecher. I don't feel like
你知道，他是个游戏玩家。 我感觉
I'm seeing a huge difference when I use
使用
Opus over Sonnet or even against Gemini,
Opus 和 Sonnet 甚至和 Gemini（价格
which would be a cheaper setup. So, I'm
更低）相比，并没有太大的区别。 所以，目前我对
kind of happy enough to be on the $20
20 美元的
pro pricing for now. Um, but I'm going
专业版定价还算满意。 嗯，但我还要
to do some more testing and see if Opus
做一些测试，看看 Opus 是否
really wins out or where it wins out.
真的能胜出，或者它在哪些方面胜出。
Maybe it works better larger code bases
也许它在大代码库
or in autonomous actions. So I'm going
或自主操作中效果更好。 所以我
to click the subscription mode here and
点击这里的订阅模式，然后就
I can just hit enter. I'm going to
可以按回车键了。 我将
accept the default here and again we
接受默认设置，并且我们
need to accept the trust of the folder.
需要再次接受对该文件夹的信任。
So two different commands here that are
这里有两个很有
helpful. You can switch between plan
用的命令。 您
mode and regular mode by just hitting
只需按下Shift+Tab键即可在计划模式和普通模式之间切换
shift tab. I can hit question mark to
。 我可以按问号键来
give me a list of common commands. And
查看常用命令列表。
then if I hit slash I can get more
然后，如果我按下斜杠，我还可以获得更多
commands as well that I can run and run
命令，我可以逐个运行这些命令
down through the list. So, I'm just
。 那么，我现在就
going to quit out of the terminal for
退出终端
now. And so, I'm just going to create a
。 所以，我打算
new folder on my hard drive. Usually, I
在我的硬盘上创建一个新文件夹。 通常情况下，我会把
open this up in a development folder
它放在电脑上某个开发文件夹里打开
somewhere on my machine. So, let's just
。 那么，我们就
create an empty folder. And then from
创建一个空文件夹吧。 然后，
cursor, I'm going to open that folder.
我将从光标处打开该文件夹。
So, in cursor, I'm going to open a new
所以，在光标模式下，我将打开一个新的
terminal window. So, just go up to the
终端窗口。 所以，只需打开
menu, type in new terminal. And
菜单，输入“新建终端”即可。
important to note that you can see up
需要注意的是，您可以看到，
here that the root of our folder is that
我们文件夹的根目录就是
folder that we opened. So, I've called
我们打开的那个文件夹。 所以我把
it invoicebot one. So, in here, we're
它命名为发票机器人一号。 所以，在这里，我们
just going to type in claude, and that
只需输入 claude，它
should kick it off. Do I want to trust
就会启动。 我是否要信任
this folder? Yes. And we're all set up.
这个文件夹？ 是的。 一切准备就绪。
Now, usually when I'm in cursor, I'll be
现在，通常当我使用光标时，我会在
using my chat window here, and I'll
这里使用我的聊天窗口，然后我会
basically tell it to create a new
告诉它创建一个新的
next.js application. Now trying that
next.js 应用程序。 现在
here in Claude uh it doesn't work as
在 Claude 中尝试这样做，嗯，效果不太好，
well because what Claude will do is it
因为 Claude 会
creates a set of files in the root
在根目录中创建一组文件，
directory that it uses for configuration
用于配置，
before it starts to do anything else.
然后再开始执行任何其他操作。
And when you're installing Nex.js, it
当您安装 Nex.js 时，
will uh give an error if it tries to
如果尝试将其
install in a a folder that already has
安装到已有内容的文件夹中，则会报错
anything in there. So the workaround is
。 所以，解决方法就是
just to open up a new terminal and just
打开一个新的终端，然后
run the setup for Nex.js yourself. It's
自己运行 Nex.js 的安装程序。
just one line, so it's easy to do. So,
只需要一行代码，所以很容易做到。 所以，
mpx create next app latest. And this
mpx 创建了下一个最新的应用程序。 这个
little dot tells it to install in this
小点告诉它安装到这个
particular folder. And just hit return.
特定的文件夹中。 然后直接按回车键。
And then we'll follow through on the
然后我们将执行默认
defaults.
设置。
Now, you'll see everything is installed
现在，您可以看到所有文件都已安装在
here in our file directory on the left
左侧的文件目录中
hand side. And if I want to test this
。 如果我想测试
out, I just hit npm rundev and will give
一下，只需运行 npm rundev，就能
me a little development server that we
得到一个小型开发服务器，我们
can start working on. And that will open
可以开始在上面工作了。 它会
on localhost 3000. So if I commandclick
在本地主机 3000 端口打开。所以如果我按住 Command 键
on that, it should open up my browser
点击它，它应该会在这里打开我的浏览器，
here and we've got our little Nex.js app
我们的 Nex.js 小应用就
ready to go. Perfect. So a useful
准备就绪了。 完美的。 因此，
command when you're stepping into a new
当你使用 Claude 进入一个新的
codebase with Claude is just type
代码库时，一个有用的命令就是输入
slashinit.
slashinit。
So type slashinit and this will
所以输入 slashinit，这将
initialize a new claude uh markdown file
初始化一个新的 claude uh markdown 文件，其中
with codebase documentation. So
包含代码库文档。 所以，
essentially what this will do is scan
它本质上会扫描
through your existing code base and
你现有的代码库，并
for it which is useful for it uh when it
为其创建一个代码审查文件或 Markdown 文件，这在它
starts to uh interact with your project
开始与你的项目进行
on an ongoing basis. So we can already
持续交互时非常有用。 所以我们已经可以
see here how Claude is working. It's got
看到克劳德是如何工作的了。 它像
the same way that cursor or any other
Cursor 或任何其他
agent would. It's able to list files,
代理一样，可以访问多种不同的工具。 它可以列出文件、
read files, create files, um, write to
读取文件、创建文件、写入
files, and search using different GP
文件，还可以使用不同的GP
patterns as well. Doing all this to
模式进行搜索。 做这一切是为了
understand, um, your codebase. And you
了解你的代码库。
can see up here now we have a difference
现在您可以看到，我们已经创建了一个不同的
view created. So we have this file
视图。 我们现在有了这个文件，
green here is what's been added in. So
绿色部分是新增的内容。
this is giving us a quick overview of
这可以让我们快速了解
our project.
项目概况。
So, as a default, Claude is going to ask
因此，默认情况下，Claude 会请求
your permission to run any of the tools.
您的许可才能运行任何工具。
So, in this case, it says, "Do you want
所以，在这种情况下，它会问：“您希望
me to make this edit to the file?" So, I
我对文件进行此编辑吗？” 所以，我
have options here. I can click yes. I
还有几个选择。 我可以点击“是”。 我
can click yes and don't ask me again in
可以点击“是”，这样本次会话中就不要再问我了；
this session or I want to do something
或者我想做点
differently. So, when you're starting
别的。 所以，当你刚开始的时候
out, I recommend you don't go into auto
，我建议你不要开启自动
accept mode. It's a good idea just to
接受模式。
understand what's happening at each
了解每个
stage. As you get more proficient and
阶段发生的事情是很有必要的。 随着你越来越熟练、
more comfortable, you can switch on the
越来越得心应手，你可以开启
auto accept mode, which just moves a
自动接受模式，这样速度就会
whole lot faster. But that can also get
快得多。 但这也可能给
you into trouble as well. It'll go off
你带来麻烦。 它会朝着
in directions that you didn't
你意想不到的方向发展
anticipate. So, we have the same thing
。 所以，
in cursor. Um, it used to be called the
光标处的情况也一样。 嗯，它以前被称为“
yolo mode or you only live once. Um, but
YOLO模式”，或者“人生只有一次”。 嗯，但是
now it has different rules for accepting
现在它对接受各种要运行的命令有不同的规则
are going to be run. So you have a
。 因此，您可以
choice at a granular level to select
细粒度地选择要
what commands do get run, what are okay,
运行的命令、哪些命令可以运行、
and what should never be um allowed to
哪些命令绝对不能
be run automatically. So I'm just going
自动运行。 所以，我暂时就回答“是”吧
to go with yes here for now.
。
So no matter what project I'm working
所以无论我做什么项目
on, I'm always going to have a quick
，一开始我都会先
chat at the start with a product manager
和产品经理进行一次简短的沟通
agent. And when I mean agent, basically
。 而我所说的代理，基本上
it's just a simple prompt that I have
只是我
created and use on most projects to give
创建并在大多数项目中使用的一个简单的提示，
a starting point for my developer agent.
为我的开发者代理提供一个起点。
I'll leave a link in the description to
我会在描述中留下
these prompts, but for now I'm just
这些提示的链接，但现在我只想先
going to run this. So you'll see I've
运行这个。 你会看到我
just created this folder here, Docs
刚刚在这里创建了这个文件夹，Docs
agents, and I've got my product manager
agents，而且我在这里放了我的产品经理
markdown prompt here. And in claude as
Markdown 提示符。 在 Claude 中，由于
it's connected to the IDE, you'll see
它与 IDE 连接，你会看到
that I have a reference to the current
我有一个对当前
file that's open. You're in the product
打开文件的引用。 您目前在产品
manager MDE. And if you just want to
经理 MDE 中。 如果您只想
check your IDE setup, you can just type
检查您的 IDE 设置，只需
in / IDE, hit return, and you can see
输入 /IDE，按回车键，即可看到
that it's selected as cursor at the
它目前已被选为光标
moment. So with my cursor in here,
。 所以，当我的光标在这里时，
you'll see that it's now referencing
你会看到它现在引用的是
this particular file with claude. So I
claude 的这个特定文件。 所以我
can say run this prompt. So you can see
可以建议运行这个提示符。 所以你可以在
the response here. Please explain your
这里看到回复。 请向我介绍一下你的
project to me. What product or
项目。
application are you looking to build?
您想开发什么产品或应用？
And so I'm just going to give it my idea
所以，我打算把我的想法告诉它，
for what it is that I want to build. And
我想建造的是什么。
I'm just going to use some voice
我打算
dictation using Whisper Flow to do that.
用 Whisper Flow 的语音输入功能来完成这项工作。
So I've got my prompt pasted in there.
我已经把提示信息粘贴进去了。
You can pause it if you want to take a
如果你想查看一下，可以暂停播放
look. And I'm just going to hit return.
。 我这就按回车键。
So it's given me a list of questions.
所以它给了我一份问题清单。
And typically they're numbered. So, I'll
而且它们通常都有编号。 所以，我就
just answer them with short answers like
用这样的简短回答来回答他们吧
this. Cool. So, it's given me my
。 凉爽的。 所以，它给了我
elevator pitch, my primary users, my
电梯演讲稿、我的主要用户、我的
characteristics, my functional
特点、我的功能
requirements, all the different headers
需求，以及
that I needed just to get started,
我入门所需的所有不同标题，
including user stories. And as per my
包括用户故事。 按照我的
prompt, it's gone and created an output
提示，它创建了一个输出
docs folder and it's given me that PRD
文档文件夹，并给了我一个
that we can reference going forward.
我们可以在以后参考的 PRD 文件。
Now, by typing the at@ symbol, I can
现在，通过输入@符号，我可以引用
reference any file that I want. So I've
任何我想要的文件。 所以我在
typed in at here and PR has given me the
这里输入了内容，PR 就给了
actual file that I want. So if I hit
我想要的文件。 所以如果我按下
return, it's given me the full context.
回车键，就能看到完整的上下文。
It's given me the full file.
它给了我完整的文件。
Now this is a nice feature of clawed
这是最近发布的爪形代码的一个不错的特性
code that was released recently. I can
。 我可以
switch into plan mode. So if you type
切换到计划模式。 所以，如果你按下
shift and tab, you can switch into plan
Shift和Tab键，就可以切换到计划
mode. And I've got my attached PRD. So
模式。 我附上了我的产品报告。 所以
I'm just going to hit return. So I have
我直接按回车键。 所以，我可以选择
the option here of accepting this plan
接受这个方案，
or I can click no and keep planning. So
也可以点击“否”继续制定计划。 那就
let's just click that. So I'm just
点击这里吧。 所以，我在
saying here for the MVP, let's keep
这里想说的是，对于MVP来说，让我们保持
things simple. So this is something
简单。 所以，
important as you're developing with AI.
在进行人工智能开发时，这一点非常重要。
So what we're going to do here instead
所以，我们不会一次性
of building out the whole app with one
构建整个应用程序，而是将
shot, we're going to break it down into
其分解成
smaller sections into an MVP. We want to
更小的部分，构建一个最小可行产品 (MVP)。 我们想
see if we can just get the main
看看能否先实现主要
functionality working so that we can
功能，以便我们可以找
just test it out with a couple of users.
几个用户进行测试。
database attached at this point. So you
目前我们并不一定需要连接数据库。 所以你
can see here it's come back with a more
可以看到，
refined plan based on my feedback. So
根据我的反馈，他们提出了一个更加完善的方案。 所以
you could go again to refine it further,
你还可以再进一步完善它，
but I think this is kind of enough for
但我认为对于最小
the MVP. So as you start out, best to
可行产品（MVP）来说，这已经足够了。 所以，刚开始的时候，最好
keep it simple so you're understanding
保持简单，这样你才能理解
everything that you're working through.
你正在学习的所有内容。
So I'm just going to accept this plan.
所以我决定接受这个计划。
So you can see here that Claude keeps a
所以你可以看到，克劳德这里有个
to-do list scratch pad. So, basically,
待办事项便笺本。 所以，基本上，
it's got an updated list of to-do that
它有了一份更新后的待办事项清单，
it will actually start to work through.
它将开始着手处理这些事项。
You'll note or you'll have heard of
你会注意到，或者你可能听说过
maybe other tools like taskmaster
Taskmaster
or windsurf now has a planning mode
或 Windsurf 等其他工具现在都有规划模式，其中
where it has a mixture of two different
混合了两种不同的
models which will do long-term planning
模型，可以
and short-term planning around your task
围绕你的任务列表进行长期规划和短期规划
list. Uh to be honest, how I normally
。 说实话，我通常
handle it in cursor is I just have a
在 Cursor 中处理这个问题的方式是，我附加一个
rules file that I attach that says, you
规则文件，其中规定，
know, create a task list if it doesn't
如果任务列表不存在，则创建一个任务列表，
exist and update that task list as we
并在我们进行规划阶段时更新该任务列表
proceed through our planning stages. It
。 事情
doesn't need to be any more complicated
不必
than that. So it is nice to see it baked
比这更复杂。 很高兴看到它
in directly into cloud code. So it's
直接集成到云代码中。 所以它
asking me, do I want to install the open
问我，是否要安装
AI SDK? So I'm just going to go ahead.
OpenAI SDK？ 那我就继续吧。
So it's talking us through the process
所以它正在向我们讲解整个过程
here. It's gone and created av local
。 它已经创建了一个本地
file and put in a sample placeholder for
文件，并在其中放入了一个用于
our open AAI API key. So while that is
我们开放的 AAI API 密钥的示例占位符。 所以趁着它还在
working away there, let's go and get our
运行，我们去获取我们的
open AI key. So you need to go to
OpenAI 密钥吧。 所以你需要访问
platform.opai
platform.opai，
and go to dashboard and then go down to
进入控制面板，然后向下滚动找到
your open AI API keys. We're going to
你的 OpenAI API 密钥。 我们将
create a new secret key and then we're
创建一个新的密钥，然后
just going to copy this key and we're
复制这个密钥并
going to paste it in. So, I've pasted in
粘贴进去。我已经把
my API key there, and it's important to
我的 API 密钥粘贴到这里了，务必
keep that secret. I'll be deleting this,
妥善保管好这个密钥。
of course, before I put the video live.
当然，在发布视频之前，我会把这条信息删除。
Or will I actually remember to do that?
我真的会记得去做这件事吗？
Who knows? Maybe go test it. Now, you
谁知道呢？ 或许可以去测试一下。 现在，你
can see it's stepped through and created
可以看到它已经逐步执行并创建了
a couple of different files. So, if you
几个不同的文件。 所以，如果你
look in the left hand side here, you'll
看一下左边，你会
see that anything marked in blue here,
看到这里用蓝色标记的任何东西都是
uh, is a modified file, and anything
修改过的文件，而
with a U is basically it's unttracked or
带有 U 的任何东西基本上都是未跟踪的或
it's brand new. So this is a useful way
全新的。 所以，这是一种
of seeing you know what the model is
了解模型
adding. So it's created an API route and
添加了什么功能的有效方法。 因此，它创建了一个 API 路由和
two different endpoints one to parse one
两个不同的端点，一个用于解析，一个
to upload. It's got a file upload
用于上传。 它包含一个文件上传
component and then there is a library
组件，还有一个库
directory and uh utility for working
目录和一个用于处理
with open AI.
OpenAI 的实用程序。
Now you'll see here it's giving me a
现在你会看到，它给了我
difference view. It's showing me what's
不同的视角。 它会在遍历文件的过程中，向我显示哪些内容
being removed and what's being added as
被删除，哪些内容被添加
it makes its way through the files. And
。 这当然
so that's great, but I find that cursor
很好，但我发现光标
just has a better way of allowing me to
能让我更好地
review and check through the changes.
查看和检查更改。
What I can do here though, as it's
不过，由于它
integrated with cursor, is I can just
与光标集成在一起，我可以按住
commandclick on any of these files and
Command 键点击这些文件中的任何一个，然后
open them up in the browser above. And
在上面的浏览器中打开它们。
then I could basically look through the
然后我就可以浏览
file to see if there's anything that I
文件，看看有没有什么我
want to change. What I like to do quite
想修改的地方。 我喜欢
a bit uh with cursor uh and this is
用光标做一些事情，而
something that's missing from Claude I
Claude 似乎缺少这个功能。
guess is I might decide I want to you
比如，我可能会想高亮
know highlight a certain piece of the
显示代码的某一部分，
code like this and to get a further
比如像这样，然后进一步
explanation of how this how this works.
解释它是如何工作的。
Uh just so I'm learning as I progress.
嗯，我只是想边做边学。
So it's asked me to run lint and lint is
所以它要求我运行代码检查工具（lint），代码检查工具
just basically a way of checking the
基本上就是一种检查
code quality and that's something I'm
代码质量的方法，我很
happy for it to always run on its own.
乐意让它一直自动运行。
So I'm just going to say yes and don't
所以我只会说“是”，别再
ask me to run that again. So you'll
让我跑一遍了。 所以你会
notice when you do that a new folder
注意到，当你这样做的时候，这里会出现一个新文件夹，里面
appears up here with your claw
有你的 Claw
configurations and you're seeing here
配置，你可以在这里看到
what you have given permissions to
你授予了哪些权限
allow. Okay. So it's gone and fixed all
。 好的。 它已经修复了所有
those errors and uh it's asking me does
这些错误，然后它问我是否要
it want can it run the development
运行开发
server. Typically I don't want it to run
服务器。 通常我不希望它运行
the development server. I want to do
开发服务器。 我想
that myself. So I'm just going to say no
自己做这件事。 所以我决定拒绝，
and I'm going to run that separately.
我会单独处理这件事。
So I'm just going to go over here to
所以我这就转到
node and then I I already have it
Node.js，我之前已经让它
running from earlier on. So let's just
运行起来了。
restart it to be sure because we've done
为了确保万无一失，我们还是重新启动一下吧，因为我们已经做了
a lot of changes. So I just type in npm
很多更改。 所以我只需输入 npm
rundev to run the development server.
rundev 来运行开发服务器。
And then if we commandclick on our
然后，如果我们按住 Command 键点击本地
localhost 3000, it'll bring us to our
主机 3000 端口，就会打开
local Nex.js version. Here we have our
本地的 Nex.js 版本。 这是我们的
invoice extractor.
发票提取器。
Let's see if it works.
看看效果如何。
So I'm going to upload a invoice from
所以我要从 Notion 上传一张发票，它
telling me it's processing the invoice
告诉我正在处理发票，
and we got an error failed to parse the
但我们收到一个错误，解析
invoice. That is to be expected. Let's
发票失败。 这是意料之中的事。 我们来
see what the error might be. So there's
看看可能是什么错误。 所以
two ways you can check your errors. You
你可以通过两种方式来检查错误。 你
can go to uh commandal alt I and get
可以按 Alt+I 键打开
your browser console information just to
浏览器控制台，
see what pops up there. And so we were
看看里面会显示什么。 因此，我们
given a uh response an internal server
收到了一个内部服务器
response error on the parse. And so
响应错误，解析失败。 因此，
we'll probably get more information on
我们很可能会在终端机内获得更多相关信息
that within our terminal itself. So if
。 所以，
we look here now your development server
现在我们来看这里，你的开发服务器
terminal holds the key to most of the
终端掌握着
problems you're going to encounter. So
你将遇到的绝大多数问题的关键。 所以
basically you can just scroll through
基本上你可以滚动浏览
the trace errors and basically pick out
跟踪错误，然后选择
the part that you want. Usually that
你想要的部分。 通常，问题是
starts at the point where you see error.
从发现错误的地方开始的。
So, we can just copy that and pull down
所以，我们可以直接复制这段代码，然后把
everything to this point. And then we
到目前为止的所有内容都下载下来。 然后我们就
can copy this. Usually, what I do in
可以复制这个了。 通常情况下，我在
cursor is I just click add to chat. But
光标模式下只会点击“添加到聊天”。 但
because we're using Claude, I can just
因为我们使用的是 Claude，所以我可以直接用
control C or command C to copy that.
Control C 或 Command C 来复制它。
Let's pop back over to Claude. And then
我们再回来看看克劳德。 然后
I'm just going to paste in that
我只需把这些
information. And I'm going to add a
信息粘贴进去就行了。 我还要添加一个
prompt. Usually, if it's a small error,
提示。 通常情况下，如果是小错误，
I'll just type in something like fix or
我只会输入类似“修复”或“
change or something like that. But when
更改”之类的字样。 但是，如果遇到
it's a more detailed error that I really
更复杂的错误，我真的
haven't a clue what's going on, um, I
不知道发生了什么，嗯，我
want to get the AI to diagnose the error
希望人工智能先诊断出错误，
first and give me a couple of options to
然后给我几个
solve it. So, this does two things.
解决办法。 所以，这样做有两个作用。
Number one, it educates me on what the
首先，它让我明白了
problem is. So, I'm learning something
问题所在。 所以，我正在学习一些东西，
and uh I'm moving forward to help the
并且正在努力帮助
model itself because often times I'll
模型本身，因为很多时候我
need to go and search for something or
需要去搜索一些东西或者
do some kind of an independent research
进行一些独立研究
to help solve the problem. Uh so I often
来帮助解决问题。 所以我通常的做法是先
just say diagnose the error and don't
诊断错误，不要
jump into implementation. So because
急于实施。 因为
we're dealing with a API and parsing
我们正在处理 API 和解析
setup, I'm not exactly sure or confident
设置，所以我不太确定或确信
that using the clawed for model that
使用 clawed for 模型是否
it's got the upto-date knowledge about
掌握了有关
that API. So basically it's using what
该 API 的最新信息。 所以基本上，它是以
it's crawled from a couple of months ago
几个月前爬取的数据
as its reference. So we want to use the
作为参考。 所以我们希望利用
search capability to kind of back up its
搜索功能来佐证我们的
findings. So I'm telling it, can you
发现。 所以我想说的是，你能
search the web to back up your research?
上网搜索一下来佐证你的研究吗？
because Claude code has search built in
因为 Claude 代码内置了搜索功能，就像
the same way that cursor or winds surf
Cursor、Windssurf
or other tools have as well.
或其他工具一样。
So based on the search, Claude is still
根据搜索结果来看，克劳德仍然
pretty happy with its first option. So
对第一个选择相当满意。 所以
we're going to go ahead with that option
我们将采取方案
one. So let's just hit one and return
一。 所以我们就去一个地方，然后返回
here. So it's giving me a list of
这里。 它会列出已
changes that it applied and a confidence
应用的更改以及
rating that the app will run. I've seen
应用程序运行的置信度评级。 我
this before. So let's see how it goes.
以前见过这种情况。 让我们看看结果如何。
So I'm instantly getting a Webpack
我立刻就遇到了 Webpack
error. So I just need to restart my
错误。 所以我只需要重启
server. Okay. So let's test out our
服务器。 好的。 那么，让我们来测试一下
invoice extractor. I'm going to drop in
发票提取器。 我打算上传
a invoice from notion. It's going to
一张来自 Notion 的发票。 系统将
process that invoice. It's sending it to
处理该发票。 它正将其发送到
the open AI file storage. Then it's
开放的AI文件存储系统。 然后它会
making a call to the image API to
调用图像 API 来
extract all the information from it. And
提取图像中的所有信息。
this is spot on. It's got all the vendor
这完全正确。 它包含了所有供应商
information, invoice details, etc.
信息、发票详情等，还有
Financial summary, and that is the
财务汇总，而且
correct amount. So this is such a big
金额也正确。 这样真是太节省
timesaver. I've got so many invoices
时间了。 我的账户里有很多发票，
that come into my account that I need to
我需要将它们
reconcile against my bank account and I
与我的银行账户进行核对，并且我
need to extract all the information like
需要提取所有信息，例如
tax um exactly what the totals were so
税款，以及确切的总额，以便
that they match. And some software will
它们能够匹配。 有些软件
actually do this for you like zero, but
实际上可以像零一样帮你完成这项工作，但
it will do it in a haphazard way or it
它会以随意的方式进行，或者
will only try and do extractions based
只会尝试
on text parsing. And this is something
基于文本解析进行提取。 而且，
you could easily use in your own company
你完全可以在自己的公司里使用这项技术
to save you a ton of time or actually
来节省大量时间，或者将其
package as a product and sell on to
包装成产品出售给
other companies. So if you'd like to see
其他公司。 所以，如果您想了解
the full process for building out this
构建此
app, I'm going to cover it in my
应用程序的完整过程，我将在我的
community at switchdimension.com.
社区 switchdimension.com 上进行介绍。
The link is in the description. Another
链接在描述里。
useful thing in Clawed Code is adding
Clawed Code 的另一个实用功能是添加
memories. So let's say you like to build
内存。 假设你喜欢
your components in a certain way or
以某种方式构建组件，或者
you'd like to have the model remind you
你想让模型不断提醒你
to commit constantly. You can create
提交更改。 你可以
that memory by typing uh hash and then
通过输入“uh hash”并
just giving it a descriptive name. Now
给它起一个描述性的名称来创建该内存。
the reason you want to use a descriptive
使用描述性
name is that the model will have context
名称的原因是，模型需要上下文
to know when to call that. And you can
才能知道何时调用该名称。 您
also view all your memories by typing
还可以通过输入斜杠“memory”来查看所有回忆
slash and then memory. And then you can
。 然后你就可以
edit the clawed memory files. What would
编辑抓取的内存文件了。 如果
claude code be without MCPs? Of course,
没有 MCP，Claude Code 会是什么样子？ 当然，
Enthropic invented the MCP. So you can
MCP 是 Enthropic 公司发明的。 所以你
also add in your MCP servers. If I type
也可以添加你的MCP服务器。 如果我输入
/mcp,
/mcp，
you can manage MCP servers. I'm just
就可以管理 MCP 服务器。 我这就按回车键
going to hit return. And it's saying
。 它提示
we've no MCP servers configured. So I
我们没有配置任何 MCP 服务器。 所以我
need to step outside of claude in order
需要退出 Claude 才能
to configure my MCPS into the terminal.
在终端中配置我的 MCPS。
So I'm just going to create a new
所以我在这里创建一个新的
terminal here. and we're going to type
终端。 然后我们要
in clawed MCP and hit return. So,
输入“爪状 MCP”，然后按回车键。 所以，
there's a couple of ways to quickly add
有几种方法可以快速添加
an MCP. You've got the ability to type
MCP。 你可以
in clawed MCP add, and then I would type
输入 clawed MCP add，然后我就可以
in the commands for the MCP that I want
输入我想添加的 MCP 的命令了
to add. So, it would be npx, the name of
。 所以，它应该是 npx，
the server, and any other commands that
服务器名称，以及可能与之相关的任何其他命令
might go with it. A far simpler way to
。 更简单的方法
do it is just to add the MCPS to your
是将 MCPS 添加到您的
Clawed Desktop setup. You can type in
Clawed Desktop 设置中。 您可以
claude MCP add from Claw Desktop and
从 Claw Desktop 输入 claude MCP add，然后
just run that command and it's going to
运行该命令，它将
give you a list of the MCPs that you've
列出您
already got set up with Claude Desktop.
已在 Claude Desktop 中设置的 MCP。
So I've got context 7 there, Genttop
所以，我这里有上下文 7，Genttop
Commander. So I'm actually going to hit
Commander。 所以我打算按
space to switch off these ones, desktop
空格键把这些都关掉，
commander for now. And then we can add
暂时先用桌面命令器。 然后我们
in the rest of those by just hitting
只需按
return. And so if I go back again to my
回车键就可以添加其余内容了。 所以，如果我回到我的
project over here and if I type slashmcp
项目页面，输入 slashmcp
mcp, I'm still not getting any servers
mcp，我仍然找不到任何服务器
in there as well. So I'm just going to
。 那我这就
exit out. So I'm just going to type in
退出。 所以我直接输入
exit.
exit 就行了。
So I would just type claude-
所以我只需输入 claude-
c to continue again. And then it's
c 即可继续。 然后它
saying no MCP servers configured. And I
提示未配置 MCP 服务器。 然后我再
just type in MCP again and see what it
输入一次MCP，看看会
gets. Yeah. And because we've um because
得到什么结果。 是的。 因为
we've restarted the terminal instance,
我们已经重启了终端实例，
we can now see them all connected. Out
现在我们可以看到它们都已连接。
of interest, these are some great MCPS
顺便提一下，这些是目前一些很棒的MCPS
at the moment. Browser MCP allows your
。 浏览器 MCP 允许您的
allows cloud code or cursor to go and
云代码或光标访问并
check on the actual app itself to see if
检查实际应用程序本身，以查看
it's running okay or to take
其是否运行正常或截取
screenshots. and context 7 goes and
屏幕截图。 上下文 7 会
searches all the recent documentation
搜索
for whatever you're trying to install or
您正在尝试安装或
set up. So now Claude will have access
设置的任何内容的最新文档。 现在克劳德也能访问
to those. And how I would invoke that is
这些资源了。 而我调用它的方式
I would basically say, you know, um use
基本上是，你知道，嗯，使用
the browser MCP to uh check the console
浏览器 MCP 来检查控制台
logs or use context 7 to find the most
日志，或者使用上下文 7 来查找
recent documentation.
最新的文档。
some other helpful commands. If you just
其他一些有用的命令。 如果你直接
type question mark, you'll get some of
输入问号，就能得到一些
the useful other commands that I might
我可能没有提到的其他实用命令
not have mentioned. So, we've covered
。 所以，我们已经讲解了
slash, we've covered the at for the file
斜杠，讲解了文件
path, for context, we've covered
路径的 at 符号，为了便于理解，我们也讲解了
memorization. If it's working through a
记忆。 如果程序正在处理某个
particular problem and you don't like
问题，而你不喜欢
where it's going, just hit escape twice.
它的处理结果，只需按两次 Esc 键即可。
So, double tap it and it will quit out
所以，双击它就会退出当前
of that particular run. Same thing you
运行。 和
have in cursor, you can hit stop or
光标操作一样，你可以点击停止或
reject. Um, you can set up auto accept
拒绝。 嗯，你可以设置自动接受
of the edits. So, you'll note as I went
编辑。 所以，你会注意到，在我操作的过程中
through, I made sure to accept each edit
，我确保每次修改都立即接受，
as it happened because I wanted to know
因为我想
exactly what was going on. You can click
确切地知道发生了什么。 您可以按
shift tab to auto accept those edits.
Shift+Tab键自动接受这些修改。
And if you're typing a prompt and you
如果你正在输入提示符，
want to get a new line, just type shift
想要换行，只需按下 Shift 键
and return and you'll get multiple new
和回车键，就能在输入较长提示符的过程中获得多行新
lines as you progress through um a
行
longer prompt.
。
So you can also paste images from your
所以你也可以直接将剪贴板中的图片粘贴
clipboard directly into the CLI. So just
到命令行界面 (CLI) 中。 所以，直接
copy whatever you have in terms of a
复制你截取的
screenshot. And instead of hitting
屏幕截图就行了。
commandV on a Mac, you need to hit
在 Mac 上，你需要按
controlV or you can actually give
ControlV 而不是 CommandV，或者你可以直接输入
reference to the actual file address and
文件的实际地址，然后
just hit return.
按回车键。
And you can see here it successfully
你可以看到，它成功地
gave me feedback on what I pasted in.
给了我粘贴内容的反馈。Entropic
here on some common workflows that are
这里有一些关于常见工作流程的优秀文档，
well worth uh taking a look at and they
非常值得一看，它们
apply to any AI assisted development
适用于任何 AI 辅助开发
workflow. Some of the things I like are
工作流程。 我喜欢的一点是，
the fact that you can go and run Claude
你可以让 Claude
in non-interactive mode. So, what we've
以非交互模式运行。 所以，我们
been doing is interacting with Claude in
一直在做的是以对话的方式在终端中与 Claude 进行交互
the terminal in a conversational manner,
，
but you can actually decide to run
但实际上你可以决定让
Claude independently on smaller tasks.
Claude 独立运行一些较小的任务。
And I would say it's only good for
我认为它只适用于
smaller tasks because as you see, you
较小的任务，因为正如你所看到的，
need to work with the model on anything
对于任何复杂的任务，你都需要与模型配合，
that's complex to help uh keep moving it
以帮助其继续推进
along.
。
If you've quit out of claude at any
如果你在任何时候退出了 Claude
point, I mentioned that you can use
，我提到过你可以使用
claude continue to pick up on the same
Claude Continue 继续之前的
session or you can actually use claude
会话，或者你可以使用 Claude
resume and you'll get a conversation
Resume，它会提供一个对话
picker when you can decide, you know,
选择器，你可以选择
which conversation you want to pick up
你想继续哪个对话
on. If you are a power user and you
。 如果您是高级用户，并且
can't be bothered waiting the 30 seconds
懒得等待 30 秒
for the model to come back to you, you
让模型返回给您，您
can actually decide to use something
可以选择使用一种
called uh work trees, which you can do
叫做工作树的功能，您可以使用
this with any tool. This isn't exclusive
任何工具来实现此功能。 这并非
to claude, but it's a nice idea where
Claude 独有的功能，但这是一个不错的想法，
you can have various different branches
你可以
of your codebase set up in a work tree.
在工作树中设置代码库的各种不同分支。
So I can actually check out independent
所以，我实际上可以查看
branches to each uh instance of claude.
每个 Claude 实例的独立分支。
So technically I could have multiple uh
所以从技术上讲，我可以同时
clawed terminals open and open working
打开多个带有爪状接口的终端，并
on various different feature branches at
在不同的功能分支上
the same time. I don't know if my brain
同时工作。 我不知道我的大脑能否
can handle that but it's an interesting
处理好这一点，但这是一个很有趣的
idea as we move more towards uh agentic
想法，因为我们正朝着使用智能体
solutions to problems and having the
解决问题的方向发展，并让
agents work on multiple things at the
智能体同时处理多项任务
same time. What is cool about claude
。  claude 最酷的地方在于它具有
scriptability because it's running in
脚本功能，这使其区别于 Cursor 或 Wind Surf 等特定 IDE，因为它在终端中运行，
the terminal and it's running as this
并且以当前
session. It's got its own SDK. It's got
会话的形式运行。 它有自己的SDK。 它
its own ability to be scripted in
本身就具备按需编写脚本的功能
whatever way you want to. So that opens
。 这便
up a whole new set of advanced use
开辟了一系列全新的高级应用
cases.
场景。
So things that I really like about
我非常喜欢
Claude is that it's really flexible. You
Claude 的一点是它非常灵活。
can add it to any IDE because it exists
由于它存在于终端中，因此您可以将其添加到任何 IDE 中
in the terminal. So you could add it to
。 所以你可以把它添加到
Jet Brains, Cursor, VS Code, whatever
JetBrains、Cursor、VS Code 或任何
tool you want. Or if you're a Vim user,
你想要的工具中。 或者，如果您是 Vim 用户，也
you can actually just run it separately
可以单独运行它
as well. So if you're a Power user and
。 所以，如果你是高级用户，并且
line most of the time, I think it's
大部分时间都习惯使用命令行，我认为它
actually a really good tool. Um the
实际上是一个非常好的工具。 嗯，
second thing is Antropic do make the
第二点是，Antropic 的确生产出了
best models or the ones that I use the
最好的模型，或者说是我
most. I rely on Claude sonnet series for
最常用的模型。 我的大部分工作都以克劳德的十四行诗系列为参考
most of the work I do. Previously it was
。 之前是
3.5. Wasn't the biggest fan of 3.7.
3.5。 我对3.7版本不太感冒。
Claude 4 isn't an improvement and it's
Claude 4 并没有改进，但它却是
the one that I used the most in terms of
我在
designing and uh developing software.
设计和开发软件方面使用最多的软件。
Um, if you're a Max user, you get a huge
嗯，如果你是 Max 用户，根据你选择的套餐，你可以获得
amount of usage up to 20x depending on
高达 20 倍的使用量，
the uh plan that you're on and you get
并且可以
unlimited access to Opus. Personally, I
无限访问 Opus。 就我个人而言，我觉得
don't find a huge difference in using
使用
Opus over using Sonnet. But that's
Opus 和使用 Sonnet 并没有太大的区别。 但这主要是
because most of the coding I do is in a
因为我大部分的编码工作都是以
interactive manner where I'm working
交互方式进行的，我需要
with the model to make changes and to
与模型互动，进行修改，并
develop out software in a prototyping
以原型设计的方式开发我们的软件
fashion. Perhaps if I was more agentic
。 也许如果我在工作中更有主见，制定好
in how I worked in that I set processes
流程，
in place and let the agent work away,
然后让代理人去工作，那么
uh, Opus might be a better choice. But
Opus 可能是一个更好的选择。 但
I've tried that in multiple different
我曾在多个不同
occasions. I run independent agents
场合尝试过。 我管理着一些独立
working on tasks. And inevitably, I feel
执行任务的代理人。 不可避免地，我觉得
like you still need a human in the loop
仍然需要有人参与进来，
to check on the work or to correct the
检查工作进展情况，或者在
model as it goes in different
模型朝着不同
directions. So, not the strongest use
方向发展时进行纠正。 所以，对我来说，这并不是最理想的应用
case for me. I really like that it's
场景。 我非常喜欢它的
scripted. scriptable. So again, it's got
剧本安排。 可编写脚本。 所以，它有
its own SDK and its own little SL or a
自己的 SDK 和自己的小型 SL 或
CLI. You can spin up multiple versions
CLI。 您可以使用 Git
in multiple different terminals and have
在多个不同的终端中启动多个版本，并使其
it working on different work threes um
在不同的工作终端上运行
with Git. So that potentially will be
。 所以这项技术未来可能会
very powerful in the future and it'll be
非常强大，
interesting to see where the team take
看看团队会如何运用它会很有意思
it. And I really like the built-in
。 我非常喜欢它内置的
planning mode. Um it really just helps
规划模式。 嗯，它确实很有帮助，
that it keeps a list of to-dos and it
因为它能帮你记录待办事项，并
helps you work through those. But again,
帮助你逐一完成这些事项。 但是，
that's something I can easily do with a
我完全可以用
rules file in cursor or wind surf um on
Cursor 或 Windsurf 之类的软件里的规则文件自己轻松实现这一点，
my own and have more control over how it
并且更好地控制它的
works because that can be quite
工作方式，因为这很大程度上取决于
opinionated to each individual person.
每个人的主观判断。
So the pros of cursor, it's a graphical
所以光标的优点在于它是一个图形
interface. So it's an IDE where you can
界面。 这是一个集成开发环境（IDE），你可以
see all the buttons where it's got
看到它
different tabs. It's very much like VS
各个选项卡中的所有按钮。 它和 VS Code 非常相似
Code. A lot of people will have learned
。 很多人都
how to program and develop using VS
通过 VS Code 学习了编程和开发
Code. So, if you're a designer, a
。 所以，如果你是一名设计师、
front-end designer, an entrepreneur
前端设计师，或者是一位
that's just getting into vibe coding or
刚刚开始接触 Vibe 编码或
AI assisted coding, I think the cursor
AI 辅助编码的企业家，我认为光标
interface is just that little bit more
界面会更加
friendly. Or you could also check out
友好一些。 或者你也可以了解一下
windsurf as well. Um, I like the fact
帆板运动。 嗯，我喜欢
that I don't have to go and learn a list
不用去学习一长串
of commands. If you're that kind of
命令这一点。 如果你是那种
person who is more designorientated or
更注重设计的人，或者
uh isn't a uh full stack constant
呃，不是那种每天都从事全栈
day-to-day developer, um you might not
开发的程序员，呃，你可能不会很
be that comfortable living in a terminal
适应一直待在终端前
all the time. So, the fact that I don't
。 所以，
have to learn a list of commands is a
不用学习一大堆命令也算是个
bit of a bonus. Um I like the fact that
意外之喜。 嗯，我喜欢
cursor has background agents now which I
Cursor 现在有了后台代理，我
can spin up and run in the background. I
可以启动它们并在后台运行。 我
like that I've got file review. So, as
喜欢有文件审核功能。 所以，当
an agent develops out the code, uh I
一个代理开发代码时，嗯，我
like in cursor the way that I get the
喜欢 Cursor 的方式，它能让我以更
much granular level. You do get that in
精细的级别进行页面审查和文件审查。 在 Clawed 中确实可以实现这一点
clawed, but it doesn't give you the
，但它并不能让你
ability to accept specific lines of code
接受
or reject them. And it doesn't give you
或拒绝特定的代码行。 而且它没有提供
an as nice of an interface to be able to
足够友好的界面来
review the changes and accept them that
查看和接受
are being made. So I think that's a plus
所做的更改。 所以我认为这对光标来说是个加分项
for cursor. And then the biggest thing
。
if I was to throw away all of those
如果我要舍弃所有
other features is the fact that cursor
其他功能，那么最大的区别在于光标与
is model agnostic. So what does that
模型无关。 那这
mean? It means that I get to pick
意味着什么？ 这意味着我可以自由选择
whatever model that I want to use. And
使用任何我想要的模型。 而且，
there is a bit of a model war that goes
模型之间的竞争也相当激烈
on. There's different prices. There's
。 价格各不相同。 有
different use cases. And I want to be
不同的使用场景。 我希望
able to pick the best model for the job.
能够选择最适合这项工作的模型。   话
That being said, I do use Claude quite a
虽如此，我确实经常使用 Claude
bit, but I'd like to be able to use
，但我很想能够使用
Gemini. I'd like to be able to use the
Gemini。 我希望能够使用
Open AI series. And with cursor, I have
OpenAI 系列软件。 通过光标，我可以
the ability to select whatever model I
选择我需要的任何模型来完成这项
want for the job. If I'm in Claw Code,
工作。 如果我使用 Claw Code，
I'm limited to using the Claw series. If
我就只能使用 Claw 系列。 如果
I'm in Windsurf, I can only use the Open
我在 Windsurf 中，我只能使用 OpenAI
AI series of models. So my biggest win
系列模型。 因此，
for cursor over everything is the fact
光标覆盖一切对我来说最大的优势在于
that it is model agnostic and I can
它与模型无关，我可以
choose whatever model that I want. So in
选择任何我想要的模型。
a nutshell, which one is right for you?
简而言之，哪一个更适合你？
I think if you want the full toolkit and
我认为，如果你想要完整的工具包和
access to every cutting edge LLM, go
所有最前沿的LLM功能，那就选择
with cursor. probably more suited to
Curser。 可能更适合喜欢使用
vibe coders or AI assisted developers or
Vibe Code 的程序员、AI 辅助开发人员，或者
people who are just getting into
刚刚开始
prototyping or starting their journey
原型设计或
with developing applications because it
应用程序开发之旅的人，因为它
mimics how VS Code works um on so many
在很多不同层面上都模仿了 VS Code 的工作方式
different levels. If you're more of an
。 如果你是一位更
advanced developer, you like living in
高级的开发者，喜欢在
the terminal and you like the idea of
终端中工作，喜欢
scripting multiple different agents and
编写多个不同代理的脚本并
having them running different processes,
让它们运行不同的进程，
then Claude could be a good step for you
那么 Claude 可能是一个不错的选择，
because on the various different Max
因为在各种不同的 Max
plans, you get a ton of usage for it to
套餐中，
uh work through in the background if
如果
you're running multiple different
你运行多个不同的
agents. So, personally, I think I'll be
代理，它就能在后台运行大量的任务。 所以，就我个人而言，我认为我会在
using cursor for the bulk of my full
我的大部分全
stack development, especially the
栈开发中使用 cursor，尤其是
interactive stuff. But when it comes to
交互式部分。 但是，对于
spinning up agents or having background
启动代理或
processes running, I'm going to continue
运行后台进程，我将继续
to explore Claude, keep it open in the
探索 Claude，让它在终端中保持打开状态
terminal, and use it where it's best
，并在最适合的地方使用它
suited. So, if you've been using Claude
。 所以，如果您已经使用 Claude
code for a while, I would love to get
代码一段时间了，我很想听听
your opinions on what your favorite
您对它最喜欢哪些
features are and what the strongest use
功能以及它最强大的应用
cases are for you. If you can add them
场景的看法。 如果你能
down into the comments, I'll call them
在评论区补充，我会
out and feature them in a future
在以后的文章中提及并重点介绍它们。